Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Photographs and Audio-Visual Materials. PHOTOS.240
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Photographs, 1880-2006., 1960-2000
  - Subseries I-A: Events and Places, 1888-2006., 1970-2000
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Los Angeles Office Millenium Party (color), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Opening (color), Nov 1998 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Opening (photographs without clients) (color), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Percy Williams Cottage, Islip Grange/Sayville, New York: Exterior (b&w), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Physician Volunteers for the Arts (color), Mar 25, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Physician Volunteers for the Arts: Lecture (color), Mar 13, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Producers Guild: Benefit (b&w), Nov 10, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Publicity Photographs: Ballet Nacional de España (production shots) (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Publicity Photographs: Ballet Nacional de España (production shots) (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Publicity Photographs: Bolshoi Ballet: "Giselle" (production shots) (b&w), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Publicity Photographs: Bolshoi Ballet: "The Golden Age" (production shots) (b&w), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Publicity Photographs: Bolshoi Ballet: "Raymonda" (production shots) (b&w), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Publicity Photographs: "A Chorus Line" and Michael Bennett (production shots) (b&w), 1975-1989 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Publicity Photographs: Famous People Players: "A Little Like Magic" (production shots) (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Publicity Photographs: "Guys and Dolls" (production shots) (b&w), 1992 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Publicity Photographs: "Honky Tonk Nights" (production shots) (b&w), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Publicity Photographs: "Insert Foot" (starring Christina Saffran) (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Publicity Photographs: National Ballet of Canada: "Alice" (production shots) (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Publicity Photographs: National Ballet of Canada: "Blue Snake" (production shots) (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Publicity Photographs: National Ballet of Canada: Headshots of Company Members (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Publicity Photographs: National Ballet of Canada: "La Ronde" (production shots) (b&w), Nov 1987 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Publicity Photographs: National Ballet of Canada: "Onegin" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Publicity Photographs: "On the Twentieth Century" (production shots) (b&w), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Publicity Photographs: "The Pajama Game" (production shots) (b&w), 1950s (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "Cinderella" (production shots) (b&w), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: Headshots of Company Members (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "In the Middle, Somewhat Elevated" and "Hot House: Thriving on a Riff" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "Lecons de Tenebres" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "Le Martyre de Saint Sebastien" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "The Nutcracker" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: Students of the School of Ballet (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Publicity Photographs: Paris Opera Ballet: "Swan Lake" (production shots) (b&w), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Publicity Photographs: "Surf City, The Beach Boys Musical" (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Publicity Photographs: Unidentified Ballet Production Shot by Martha Swope (b&w), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Publicity Photographs: Unidentified Production Shot by Martha Swope Associates (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Publicity Photographs: Various Broadway Productions and Actors' Headshots (labeled) (b&w), 1950s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - RAI, Italian Television: Presentation of Check to Actors' Fund (b&w), Mar 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Salute to Barnard Hughes (?), Held at Connecticut Home of Lois and Jason Robards, Jr. (color), Jan 2002 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Season of Concern, Chicago, Illinois: Summer Suburban Bowl-O-Rama (color), Aug 12, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Streamers Softball in San Francisco (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Submission to Willard Scott Birthdays, TODAY Show, NBC News for Unidentified Person (includes response to submission) (color), ca. 2003 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Takarazuka Revue Company at Radio City Music Hall (b&w), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Tammany Hall, New York, New York (b&w), 1904 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Theatre De Lys: 25th Anniversary "Broadway Salutes Off-Broadway" (b&w), Sep 29, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Times Square (Longacre Square), New York, New York (b&w), 1900-1936 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Tony Awards (color), Jun 10, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Unidentified (b&w), most undated (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Unidentified (color), most undated (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Unidentified Event: House Party (color), Jul 22, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 351)
    - Unidentified Event in California: "20 Twenty" (photograph exhibition?) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - Unidentified Events in Los Angeles, California (including daytime TV stars and a birthday celebration) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - Unidentified Event: Liza Minelli and Others Receiving Award (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - Unidentified Event: Michael Feinstein Performing at Kate Johnson's (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - Unidentified Event: "The Women" (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Union Square Theatre (copy photograph) (b&w), 1888 (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - Vorpal Art Gallery: Benefit Party (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Works Progress Administration (WPA) Theater Project: New Jersey (b&w), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Subseries I-B: People, 1880-2005., 1960-2000
    - Abbot, George (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - Adams, William P. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - Albee, Edward F. (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 362)
    - Aldrich, Louis, Al Hayman and Henry Miner (Presidents) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - Alexander, John (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Arroyo, Martina (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 365)
    - Astor, Philip (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Bacall, Lauren (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Barrymore, Ethel (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Beck, Louise: Birthday Party (b&w), Feb 1997 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Beck, Martin and Louise Beck (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - Benedict, Paul and Al Pacino (at unidentified event) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - Benham, Earl (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - Benincasa, Joseph P. (Executive Director) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Benincasa, Joseph P. and Harold "Hal" Prince (color), Jun 19, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - Birsh, Arthur T. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Board of Trustees: Unidentified (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - Booth, Edwin (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Bradin, Nicole: Biographical Sketch and Headshots for Shape Magazine (b&w), 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - Brown, A.O. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Bullock, Jim and Don (at unidentified event) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Campbell, Robert (General Manager & Treasurer) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - Caron, Leslie (b&w), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - Caruso, Tony, Diane Ladd and Lynn Wood (b&w), Oct 1983 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - Charles, Richard L. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - Clark, Winnie: 100th Birthday at Actors' Fund Home (color), Oct 16, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 385)
    - Cohan, George M.: Presentation of Donation to Actors' Fund (copy photographs) (b&w); Portrait (b&w), 1919, undated (Box 7, Folder 386)
    - Cohen, Alexander H. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Cronkite, Walter (b&w, color), undated (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - Cronyn, Hume (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - Davion, Alex (in "The Caretaker") (b&w), Nov 19, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Debuskey, Merle (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - De Liagre, Alfred Jr. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Del Tredici, David (composer) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Dewhurst, Colleen (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - Dillon, Tom (President) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - Dillon, Tom (President): In Group Shots at Various Events (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - Di Tolla, Alfred W. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - Drescher, Fran (at unidentified event) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - Duncan, Pamela (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 399)
    - Duncan, Pamela and Tessie Marino Richner (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 400)
    - Dupuy, Diane (Founder and Artistic Director of Famous People Players) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Eisenberg, Alan (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 402)
    - Eric, David (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 403)
    - Evans, Maurice (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 404)
    - Executive Committee (Bob Adams, John Alexander, Nedda Logan Harrigan, Warren P. Munsell and Louise Beck) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 405)
    - Factor, Mallory (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 406)
    - Famous People Players (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - Fiske, Harrison Grey (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 408)
    - Frohman, Daniel (President & Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 409)
    - Gish, Lillian (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 410)
    - Glover, Savion (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 411)
    - Goldberg, Whoopi (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 412)
    - Goodstein, Jacob J. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 413)
    - Gordon, Max (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 414)
    - Gordoni, Virginia (b&w), undated, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 415)
    - Greaza, Walter N. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 416)
    - Grigorovich, Yuri (Artistic Director of Bolshoi Ballet) (b&w), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 417)
    - Guettel, Henry (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 418)
    - Guillaume, Robert (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 419)
    - Hagel, Conrad (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 420)
    - Hagman, Larry (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 421)
    - Harper, Valerie (color), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 422)
    - Harrison, Rex (photograph donated by Charlet Oberley) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 423)
    - Hart, Kitty Carlisle (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 424)
    - Hayes, Helen (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 425)
    - Hayes, Helen: 80th Birthday (b&w), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 426)
    - Hayes, Helen: 80th Birthday Party, Headshots and Movie Production Shots (b&w), 1931-1980 (Box 7, Folder 427)
    - Hepburn, Katharine (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 428)
    - Herlihy, Ed (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 429)
    - Herrmann, Edward (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 430)
    - Hewitt, Alan (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 431)
    - Hill, Elaine Welton (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 432)
    - Hollerith, Charles Jr. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 433)
    - Holm, Celeste (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 434)
    - Hughes, Barnard (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 435)
    - Hundley, John Walker (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 436)
    - Jackson, Anne (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 437)
    - Jacobs, Bernard (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 438)
    - Jacobs, Michael (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 439)
    - Jacobson, Stuart: Book Party at Macy's for "Only the Best: A Celebration of Gift Giving in America" (b&w), Nov 13, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 440)
    - Johnson, Janice: Actors' Work Program Profile (used in Annual Report) (b&w), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 441)
    - Kiley, Richard (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 442)
    - Klaw, Marc (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - Krones, Fred (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 444)
    - Krull, Linda (at unidentified event) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - Kuralt, Charles (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 446)
    - Lane, Nathan (speaking at unidentified event) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 448)
    - Lawrence, Shubert Jr. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 448)
    - Le Noire, Rosetta (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 449)
    - Levene, Sam (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 450)
    - Logan, Nedda Harrigan (President) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 451)
    - Lortell, Lucille (b&w), undated, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 452)
    - Lotito, Louis A. (President) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 453)
    - Louise, Mary: Performing in "Love and Laughter" and "Music of Eubie Blake" at Actors' Fund Home (color), Dec 19, 2002-Mar 2, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 454)
    - Lowe, Jim and Smith Street Band: Performing at Actors' Fund Home (color), Aug 12, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 455)
    - Lurie, Louis R. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 456)
    - MacLaine, Shirley (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 457)
    - Mark, Erica (Director of Development): Party (color), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 458)
    - Marshall, Armina (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 459)
    - Martin, David (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 460)
    - Mayer, John: Performance and Interview on Times Talks (color), Jan 12, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 461)
    - McCarthy, Frances, Party for (b&w), Mar 18, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 462)
    - McGlinn, Frank C.P. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 463)
    - Mearian, Mike (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 7, Folder 464)
    - Mitchell, Brian Stokes (President) (color), undated (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - Moon, Beata (at unidentified event) (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 466)
    - Munroe, Wallace (Director of Public Relations) (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 467)
    - Munsell, Warren P. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 468)
    - Nederlander, James M. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 469)
    - Newman, Paul (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 470)
    - Nicholas, Fayard (Nicholas Brothers), John Bubbles (Buck and Bubbles) and Al Williams (Tip, Tap and Toe) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 471)
    - Oberon, John (autographed) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 472)
    - O'Connor, Nancy (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 473)
    - Office Staff: California and New York Offices (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 474)
    - Office Staff: California and New York Offices (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 475)
    - Office Staff: Dan and LeRoy's Going Away Lunch (color), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 476)
    - Office Staff: Joe, Ariel Braun, and Wallace Munroe (b&w), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 477)
    - Office Staff: Megan's Baby Shower (color), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 478)
    - Office Staff: Melissa's Goodbye Party (color), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 479)
    - Office Staff: Richard Rodgers Presents Life Membership in Actors' Fund to Staff of Long Service (b&w), Dec 1965 (Box 8, Folder 480)
    - Office Staff: Unidentified (color), Aug 1984 (Box 8, Folder 481)
    - Office Staff: Unidentified: Chicago Office (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 482)
    - Olson, Dale (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 483)
    - Paige, Janis (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 484)
    - Paige, Janis (in production shots of "Mame") (b&w), 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 485)
    - Palmer, Albert M. (President) (b&w), 1893 (Box 8, Folder 486)
    - Pataki, George (Governor of New York): Signing of New York State Legislature Bill (pertaining to actors' health coverage) (b&w), Sep 13, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 487)
    - Pataki, George (Governor of New York): Signing of New York State Legislature Bill (pertaining to actors' health coverage) (color), Sep 13, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 488)
    - Perry, Blanche Collins and Luther Perry (color), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 489)
    - Peters, Bernadette (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 490)
    - Powers, David A. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 491)
    - Prince, Harold "Hal" (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 492)
    - Raymond, Larry and Marion Lee (The Raymonds) (includes accompanying correspondence) (b&w), undated, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 493)
    - Rockettes (Radio City Music Hall) (b&w), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 494)
    - Sabinson, Harvey (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 495)
    - Sappington, Harriet (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 496)
    - Sardi, Vincent: Presentation of Check in Memory of (b&w), Dec 9, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 497)
    - Schwartz, Sam (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 498)
    - Scribner, Sam (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 499)
    - Shepard, Dick (color), Sep 7, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 500)
    - Shipley, Thomas: Carbaret at Broadway Grill (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 501)
    - Shubert (Lee, John and Milton) and Robert Christenberry, undated (Box 8, Folder 502)
    - Sills, Beverly: Costume Shots (b&w), May 17 - Jul 15, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 503)
    - Simon, Louis M. (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 504)
    - Simon, Louis M.: Blood Award (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 505)
    - Simon, Louis M. (Head & Shoulders) (b&w), Jan 1973 (Box 8, Folder 506)
    - Simon, Louis M.: Retirement Party (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 507)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 508)
    - Smith, Joe (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 509)
    - Smith, Joe and Charlie Dale (Smith and Dale) and Red Buttons at Actors' Fund Home (b&w), May 1971 (Box 8, Folder 510)
    - Smith, Liz (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 511)
    - Smith, Marsha (Western Representative) (b&w), Apr 1988 (Box 8, Folder 512)
    - Southern, Hugh (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 513)
    - Sponder, Wanda (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 514)
    - Stapleton, Jean (Trustee) (b&w), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 515)
    - Stewart, James (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 516)
    - Straight, Beatrice (Trustee) (b&w), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 517)
    - Stritch, Elaine (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 518)
    - Swire, Willard (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 519)
    - Tandy, Jessica (b&w), 1980s (Box 8, Folder 520)
    - Thrall, Cindy (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 521)
    - Tomkins, Don (b&w), undated, 1948-1961 (Box 8, Folder 522)
    - Tomkins, Don: Receiving Outer Circle Award and Production Shots of "Wildcat" (b&w), 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 523)
    - Trevor, Claire (b&w), 1932-1987 (Box 8, Folder 524)
    - Tunney, Gene (signed souvenir photograph) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 525)
    - Unidentified (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 526)
    - Unidentified (color) (Box 8, Folder 527)
    - Vincent, Walter (President) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 528)
    - Vinton, Freedley (President) (b&w), 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 529)
    - Vitelli, Vincent (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 530)
    - Wagstaff, Joseph (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 531)
    - Wallach, Eli (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 532)
    - Wallack, Lester (President) (b&w), 1880 (Box 8, Folder 533)
    - Waxman, Herschel (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 534)
    - Wedel, Renee (b&w), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 535)
    - White, Lillia (color), undated (Box 8, Folder 536)
    - Whitehead, Robert (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 537)
    - Wolfington, Iggie (Trustee) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 538)
    - Youngman, Henny (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 539)
  - Subseries I-C: Catholic Actors' Guild: George W. Moore Materials, 1942-1975.
    - Loose Photographs (of Mickey Rooney and others) and Clippings from Commemorative Scrapbook Celebrating the Reverend George W. Moore's 20th Anniversary of Ordination (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 540)
    - Scrapbook: George W. Moore, 20th Anniversary of Ordination (in Series IX: Scrapbooks), 1942-1975 (Box 14)
    - Cohen, George M.: Portraits and Plaque, undated (Box 14)
  - Subseries I-D: Rathbone Family, 1896-1939.
    - Garden Party (men in British Armed Forces uniforms?) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 541)
    - Party (at unidentified location) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 542)
    - Rathbone, Anna Barbara (Basil Rathbone's mother) (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 543)
    - Rathbone, Edgar Phillip (Basil Rathbone's father) (b&w), undated, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 544)
    - Rathbone, Basil: Family Portraits (Basil, brother and sister) (b&w), undated, 1896-1939 (Box 8, Folder 545)
    - Rathbone, Basil: Wedding Photographs (photocopies of oversize photographs; originals are in Box 11) (b&w), Apr 18, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 546)
    - Unidentified Places and People (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 547)
    - Unidentified Portraits (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 548)
    - Scrapbook: Basil Rathbone, European Travels (in Series IX: Scrapbooks), mid-1930s (Box 13)
  - Subseries I-E: Tremaine Twins: Edna and Evalin Burnett, 1942-1999.
    - Certificates and Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 549)
    - Funeral and Burial Arrangements at Forest Lawn Memorial, 1975-1999 (Box 8, Folder 550)
    - Production Publicity Shots I (b&w) (see also oversize photographs in Box 11), undated (Box 8, Folder 551)
    - Production Publicity Shots II (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 552)
    - Production Publicity Shots III (b&w), undated (Box 8, Folder 553)
    - Programs and Press Clippings, undated (Box 8, Folder 554)
    - Souvenir Photographs (autographed) (b&w), undated, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 555)
    - Traveling (b&w), undated, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 556)
    - Scrapbook: Edna Burnett (in Series IX: Scrapbooks), 1920s (Box 14)
    - Oversize: Tremaine Twins (Edna and Evalin Burnett): Production Publicity Shots (in Series VIII: Oversize Photographs and Contact Sheets), undated
- Series II. Electronic Files, 2000-2003
  - CD: Actors' Fund Home: Dedication of Alzheimer's Wing and Holiday Party (color, 43 JPEG format files), Dec 15, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 557)
  - CD: Benefit: Parade of Stars (color, 778 JPEG format files), Mar 10, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 558)
  - CD: Benincasa, Joseph P. (Executive Director) (color, 3 JPEG format files), undated (Box 8, Folder 559)
  - CD: Gala: "That's Entertainment" Staff Photographs (color, 51 JPEG format files), undated (Box 8, Folder 560)
  - CD: Office Staff: Headshots of Staff and Officers (color, 42 JPEG format files), undated (Box 8, Folder 561)
  - Floppy Disk: Actors' Work Program: Chemistry Department and Accounting (color, 11 JPEG format files), undated (Box 8, Folder 562)
  - Floppy Disk: AIDS Initiative (color, 12 JPEG format files), undated (Box 8, Folder 563)
- Series III. Contact Sheets, 1964-2004.
  - Subseries III-A: Contact Sheets (that have matching prints), 1964-2000.
    - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 564)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, Jan 11, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 565)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 566)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Dedication of Lucille Lortell Theatre with Performance of "Dracula" by National Players, Apr 5, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 567)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 1988 (Box 9, Folder 568)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 1991 (Box 9, Folder 569)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 23, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 570)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Dedication Ceremony, Dec 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 571)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Groundbreaking, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 572)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Home and Residents, undated (Box 9, Folder 573)